

WWW.JENNIFERBCHRISTIE COM

973 262 2632

LINKEDIN COM/IN/. JENNRC87

GITHUB.COM/JENNRC87

JENNIFER R. CHRIST

BRAND STATEMENT:

As a Full Stack Web Developer, my mission is to add value to your company. I am an excited and enthusiastic person, who's inquisitive about life. Whether it's for my job, or taking the initiative to learn on my own, I have always been hard-working. For me, passion is a key attribute that determines the outcome of your success. I have won various awards at the various companies I have worked at. Last year I won the 2015 Quarter One Best Non-sell Associate, for my outstanding contributions to my teams, and I realize that when we work together, we achieve the best results. Having lead an unorthodox career path, my personal experiences and straightforward approach, make me unique and adaptable to any situation. I want to impact the world through my imaginative approach to make life more enjoyable for people.

EXPERIENCE

General Assembly

10/2016 - 1/2017

The White Transvaal Lion: Shooting Game

HTML/CSS, JavaScript, jQuery

Designed a game that renders in the browser

Implemented logic for winning and displayed win or lose states

London Playhouse

HTML/CSS, JavaScript, Express, Mustache, Fetch, Bcrypt, Body-Parser, Curl Application pulling information from an API

Full Stack CRUD application with log in capabilities

GA Lunch Break

HTML/CSS , Ruby on Rails, Google Maps API, Javascript, Postgresql, Materialize, BCrypt, Sessions, Gon Gem

Group oriented web application that recommends local area dining Implemented logic for winning and displayed win or lose states

Lord & Taylor: Fulfillment Associate 9/2013 - 10/2016

Accurately picked e-commerce orders by style, color, and size

Shiped orders to various customers using FedEx Promoted from stock to fulfillment associate

Received the 1st Quarter Best Non-Sales Award for 2015

The Gap: Sales Associate

5/2011 - 12/2012

Organized the sales floor according to the company standards Prioritized between management tasks and assisting customers

Analyzed and solved customer problems when debating purchases

Everett Publishing: Executive Assistant 1/2011 - 5/2011
Provided executive level administrative support to the Founder

Provided executive level administrative support to the Founder Supplied sponsors for the Alex: The Magazine Relaunch Party

 $\label{lem:conditional} Arranged \ meetings, appointments \ and \ recorded \ minutes$

Researched competitors and provided ideas for rebranding

TECHNICAL SKILLS:

HTML5, CSS3, Ruby, SQL, Node.js, React.js, Express.js, Mustache.js, jQuery, Bootstrap, Ruby on Rails, Sinatra, RSpec, PostgreSQL, AJAX, ISON

Others:

Adobe Illustrator, InDesign, Photoshop

EDUCATION:

General Assembly:

Web Development Immersive

The New School:

Graphic Design

Montclair State Univeristy:

Fashion Stuides

VOLUNTEER:

Volunteers of America:

Operation Backpack Toys for the Holiday